声明: 本字幕由YYeTs美剧字幕组原创翻译制作
欢迎访问官方论坛  www.YYeTs.net 在线观看 剧情讨论 学习交流
=====本字幕由以下成员荣誉制作 感谢他们的无私奉献======
翻译：Singa校对： BillSky
后期：xyz 双语制作：DrunkBat
========== 字幕总监制：七色九天 ==========
Alex...
他们带走了我的孩子
They took my baby.
有人么  救救我
Somebody, please help me!
他拿着一种...一种像针的东西
He had this...this thing, like...like a needle,
然后刺了我
and he stabbed me with it.
他想伤害我的孩子
He was trying to hurt my baby.
我们有麻烦了  旅客名单
We got a problem. The manifest
幸存者的名单...
the names of everyone who survived...
我问了所有人  有一个人不在旅客名单上...
I interviewed everyone. One of them isn't in the manifest...
你们好
Hello there.
我想他们是被劫持了
I think they've been taken.
Claire!
我不记得Ethan
I don't remember Ethan.
我不记得他对我做了什么
I don't remember what he did to me.
救命
Help me!
别相信他说的  他是他们中的一个
Don't believe a word he says! He's one of them.
我不知道她在讲什么
I have no idea what she's talking about.
他会一直说谎
For a long time, he will lie.
我不知道为什么你问我这些问题
I don't know why you're asking me all these questions.
这全是误会
This is all a mistake.
告诉我真相  告诉我你是谁
Tell me the truth! Tell me who you are!
如果他说的是真的呢  John?
What if he's telling the truth, John?
如果不是呢?
What if he's not?
没事的  亲爱的
Hey, it's okay, sweetie.
亲爱的  没事的
Hey, sweetie, it's all right.
-John?  John?  醒醒   -什么  Claire?  怎么了?
-John? John? Wake up.  -What, Claire? What?
他烧得很厉害  并且出现皮疹了
He's burning up, and he's got a rash.
我得找到Jack
And I need to find Jack.
他  呃  他在舱里轮班
He's, uh, he's on shift at the hatch.
-好的   -呃  不  Claire  等等
-Okay.  -Uh, no, Claire, wait.
-Claire  等等   -不  不行  John  我不能等了
-Claire, wait.  -No, I can't, John, okay?
不不不  这么晚了你不能去丛林里
No, no, no. You're not walking through the jungle in the middle of the night.
我去找Jack 我马上把他带来
I'll go get Jack. I'll send him right back here.
-好的   -别担心
-Okay.  -Don't worry.
Jack
怎么了?
What's going on?
孩子发烧了
The baby's got a fever.
-发烧了?   -Claire还想亲自过来
-A fever?  -Claire was coming here.
-他睡了么?   -整晚没响过一声
-He asleep?  -Not a sound all night.
我尽快赶回来
I'll get back here as soon as I can.
亲爱的  没事的  没事的
Hey, hey, sweetie, it's okay. It's okay.
妈妈马上让你凉下来  好么? 好么?  嘘  没事的
Mommy's just gonna cool you down, okay? Okay? Shh. It's okay.
你在这儿干什么?  离我们远点
What are you doing here? You stay away from us!
他是被感染的  是么?
He's infected, isn't he?
什么?
What?
你的孩子...他病了
Your child...he's sick.
走开  离我们远点
Just get away. You get away from us!
你记不得了  是么?
You don't remember, do you?
这是疫苗  我们得防止他生病
It's a vaccine. We don't want him to get sick.
嘿  回去  离她远点
Hey, get back! Get away from her!
你来这儿想干什么?
What do you think you're doing here?
你来这儿干什么?
What are you doing here?
离开我们的营地
Just get out of our camp.
怎么了?
What happened?
她说什么了?
What did she say?
她说孩子出问题了
She said there's something wrong with him.
这不像他  他以前整晚都睡着的
It's just not like him. He always sleeps through the night.
这种皮疹...我是说  可能出问题了
And this rash...I mean, there's something wrong.
孩子病了  Claire
Babies get sick, Claire.
好吧  发烧和咳嗽怎么解释呢?
Okay, what about the fever and cough?
很正常的现象
Perfectly normal.
他已经吃不下东西了  还有...
And he hasn't been eating at all, and...
Claire  他没事的  可能得了红疹
Claire, he's okay. It's probably roseola.
在他这种年龄是很普通的病
It's a typical virus that's common in children his age,
皮疹就是一种症状
and the rash is a sign of it.
好吧  那如果不是呢?
Okay. What if it's not?
如果他得了更严重的病呢?
What if he caught something really bad?
像是感染什么的?
Like some kind of infection?
感染?  你怎么想到这个的?
Infection? Where did you get that idea?
Rousseau来过这儿
Rousseau was here.
她对你说了什么?
What did she say to you?
她说她知道他病了  他是被感染的
She said she knew he was sick, okay? That he's infected.
Claire  这不是被感染的
Claire, there is no infection.
我们在这个岛已经两个月了 没有人生病
We've been on this island for two months, and no one's gotten sick.
Rousseau有点不正常
Rousseau's crazy.
我们按发烧来治他
We're gonna let the fever just run its course.
会没事的  好么?  相信我
It's gonna be fine, okay? Trust me.
我得回去舱里
I've gotta get back to the hatch.
我会在几小时后再来看他  好么?
And I'll come back in a couple hours and check on him again, okay?
-好么?   -好的
-Okay?  -Yeah.
如果他出什么问题的话   我肯定Jack会知道的
Hey,  I'm sure that if there was something wrong, Jack would know.
你确定要这么做么? 我们和她不熟
Are you sure about this? We don't really know her.
我想她能帮我
I think she can help me.
嘿  你们好
Hey, guys.
你是神经医生  对么?
So you're a shrink, right?
我是临床心理医生   也可以说是神经医生
I'm a clinical psychologist, but "shrink" works, too.
你能帮人回忆事情么?
Can you help people remember things?
我想这取决于你想回忆什么
I guess it depends on what you need to remember.
那是我们在这个岛上的第二周
So it was our second week on the island.
我去了丛林里  并且我...
I was out in the jungle, and I...
我怀着孩子  Charlie和我在一起
I thought I was having the baby. Charlie was with me.
然后Ethan来了
And there was this man...Ethan.
我们以为他和我们一样 也是飞机上的 但却不是
We thought he was one of us from the plane, but he wasn't.
他劫持了我...他带走了我们两个 然后...
So  he took me...he took both of us. And...
我记不得了  我什么都想不起来了
I don't remember. I don't remember anything.
当Jack和我找到Charlie时 他被围着脖子吊在了树上
When Jack and I found Charlie, he was hanging from a tree by his neck.
我不知道发生了什么
I have no idea what happened,
现在我只能回想起一点点的片段
and now I'm seeing these flashes of things.
并且  你知道  我有健忘症
And, you know, I have amnesia.
两周时间就从我的生命里丢失了
There's two weeks missing from my life.
Claire  我不认为你有健忘症
Claire, I don't think you have amnesia.
你知道  有时候当一些可怕的事降临时
You know, sometimes when something terrible happens to us,
你的脑子想到的只是怎么保护自己
there's a little switch in your head that flicks on to protect us
而不是怎么去应对
from having to deal with it.
你的记忆可能还在
Maybe your memories aren't gone.
也许它们只是被阻挡在你脑子里了
Maybe you're just blocking them.
那现在我需要你来解开阻碍
Then I need you to unblock them.
因为我孩子病了  并且他们曾经对他做过什么
'Cause my baby's sick, and they did something to him.
你需要去洗澡么?
Do you have to go to the bathroom?
好 那么想去的时候和我们说一声吧
Well, just let us know when you do.
好的  我希望如此
Yeah, I'll look forward to that.
你可能想读点什么
Thought you might like something to read.
Dostoevsky的小说  你没有Stephen King的么?
Dostoevsky. You don't have any Stephen King?
这个图书馆有点过时
The library's a little outdated.
好的  谢谢
Right. Well, thanks.
干吗给他本书?
What's with the book?
让他消遣消遣
Just something to pass the time.
你知道Hemingway很妒忌Dostoevsky么?
Did you know that Hemingway was jealous of Dostoevsky?
不  John  我不知道
No, John, I didn't know that.
他想成为世界上最伟大的作家
He wanted to be the world's greatest writer
但是他却始终不能摆脱Dostoevsky的阴影
but convinced himself that he could never get out from under Dostoevsky's shadow.
很可惜  真的
Kind of sad, really.
我们该怎么做  Jack?
What are we doing, Jack?
该怎么做什么?
What are we doing?
我们不能永远把他藏在这儿
We can't hide him down here forever.
轮班的时候会有人发现的
Changing shifts around is gonna get people asking questions.
我只是想知道有什么长远打算
I just want to know what the long-term plan is.
John  我来问问你...
Well, John, let me ask you this...
对于那个按键我们没什么长远打算
we don't have a long-term plan for the button,
但是我们还是坚持去按  不是么?
but we keep pushing it, don't we?
听着  在我们知道他是谁   他说出真相以前
Look, until we know who he is, whether or not he's telling the truth,
我们该怎么做就怎么做
we have to keep doing what we're doing.
如果你有更好的主意  可以说来听听
If you've got a better idea, let's hear it.
你放我走怎么样?
How about you let me go?
现在我们清静了
Now we're away from all the noises of the camp.
呼吸
Just breathe.
全身放松
Let your whole body relax.
好的
Good.
听着海浪声
Listen to the waves.
好的  吸...
Good, in...
慢慢地呼...  好的
and out slowly. Good.
闭上眼睛
Keep your eyes closed.
放轻松  Claire
Very relaxed, Claire.
保持呼吸
Just keep breathing.
现在我要你看见你怀孕时的样子
Now I want you to visualize yourself when you were pregnant.
注意听我的声音
Keep listening to my voice.
想想你看见了什么
Think about what you see.
这是疫苗  我们得防止他生病
It's a vaccine. We don't want him to get sick.
你上一次身体检查是什么时候 Claire?
When was your last checkup, Claire?
噢  有段时间了
Oh, I haven't been in a while.
我一直很忙 而且...
I've been busy, and...
我正要去洛杉矶
I'm going to Los Angeles.
-真的么?  -是的
-Really?  -Yeah.
在你快要生的时后去旅行 这可不好
Traveling in your third trimester, that's not usually recommended.
在那儿有户人家   我...想把孩子寄养在那儿
Uh, there's a family there. I'm, uh, giving the baby up for adoption.
当然  我了解
Oh, of course. I understand.
我给你的止痛药是很轻微的
The sedative I gave you is very mild.
我知道这些测验很紧迫
I know these exams can be very stressful.
现在要给你打一针  Claire
I'm going to give you a shot now, Claire.
一点给孩子的药物
A little medicine for your baby.
别担心  你只会感到一丝刺痛
Don't worry. You're just gonna feel a little pinch.
没事的  你很好  没事的  没事的
It's okay. You're all right. It's okay. It's okay.
是Ethan  我看见Ethan了
It was Ethan! I saw Ethan!
我看到他了  是Ethan
I saw him. It was Ethan!
-Claire  Claire  没事的   -不  有事的
-Claire, Claire, it's okay.   -No, it's not!
-你很好   -不  我不好
-You're all right.  -No, I'm not all right!
-你做了什么?   -没什么  她...
-What did you do?  -Nothing, she just...
再来一次
Do it again!
不  Claire  你快发狂了
No, Claire, you were screaming.
但是我记起来了  好么?
But I remembered, okay?
-我看到了Ethan   -Claire...
-I saw Ethan.  -Claire...
他在那儿  他在给我做测验
He was there, and he was giving me an exam.
你看见的可能是你坠机前的经历
What you saw could be combining experiences of what happened before the crash
和现在岛上的经历混起来的事
to the things that happened here on the island.
不  好么  不  这是真的
No, okay, no! This was real!
我被打麻药了
I was drugged.
他对我做过什么
He did something to me.
Claire  你得冷静下来 好么?  这对你不好
Claire, you need to calm down, all right? It's not good for you.
你知道么?  Aaron病了  好么?
You know what? Aaron is sick, okay?
我得找到那个地方
I need to find that place!
那个房间...是真的  是真的
That room...it's real. It's real.
好么  那儿有药  给孩子的药
Okay, and there's medicine there. For the baby.
我要找到那地方  我要去找
I need to find it. I need to find it.
Kate  求你了  帮我找到那地方
Kate, Kate, please, help me find it.
怎么...
What's the...
-有人么?  -你好
-Hello?  -Howdy.
你好  John  你一个人么?
Hello, John. You are alone?
你来了就不是了
Not anymore.
-你们有多少...  -闭嘴
-How many of you...  -Shut up.
我想借把锯子
I was hoping to borrow a saw.
当然可以  跟我来吧
Absolutely. Right this way.
我需要把枪  你不要问我为什么
I need a gun, and you don't get to ask why.
恩  小姐  所有枪都在我这儿   我得问为什么
Well, Thelma, seeing as I got all the guns, I do get to ask why.
-不  你不需要知道   -不  我要知道
-No, you don't.  -Yes, I do.
听着
Watch.
为什么?
Why?
给我把枪  Sawyer
Just give me a gun, Sawyer.
来看看
Check it out.
我找到了一副新的眼镜  喜欢么?
I found a new pair of glasses damn near my prescription. You like 'em?
好吧  我们要去丛林里追踪Rousseau
All right, I'm going into the jungle to track down Rousseau.
那个法国人?  为了什么?
The french chick? What for?
Claire认为她知道哪里有药物
Claire thinks she knows where there might be some medicine.
孩子病了
The baby's sick.
-恩  药我这儿有   -她认为他病得很厉害
-Well, hell, I got medicine.  -She thinks he's really sick
是需要隔离的那种病
as in "quarantine" sick.
你认为呢?
What do you think?
我想她是过于担心了
I think she's a little too worried.
但是她要去追Rousseau 不管我是否同去
But she's going after Rousseau with or without me.
男人不许去  是么?
No boys allowed, huh?
好吧  你要什么? 9毫米手枪  还是来复枪?
All right, what do you want? 9 millimeter or rifle?
我不认为这是个好主意
I don't think this is a good idea.
也许你该听Jack的
Maybe you should listen to Jack.
但是如果Jack错了呢?
But what if jack's wrong, okay?
Jack说热度会降下来  但是没有 反而越来越糟了
Jack said the fever would break, and it hasn't. He's getting worse.
只是因为还没开始降  不是...
Just because it hasn't broken yet, it doesn't...
那么  我还要等多久  Sun?
Well, how long am I supposed to wait, Sun?
母亲不应该离开她的孩子的
A mother should not leave her child.
不好意思  你是母亲么?
I'm sorry. Are you a mother?
不是...
No...
我不是
I'm not.
Claire  你确定你想这么做?
Claire, are you sure you want to do this?
你说什么?
What did you say?
你确定你想这么做?
Are you sure you want to do this?
你得确定
You need to be sure.
你得离开这儿...
You have to get out of here...
你要把那个打到我肚子里么?
Do you have to put that in my tummy?
这会非常非常痛
'Cause it really, really hurts.
我知道
I know.
我希望还有其他办法
I wish there was another way.
但是孩子需要它  Claire
But the baby needs it, Claire.
好么?
Okay?
好的
Okay.
好了  可以了 不是太痛  是么?
There, all done. That wasn't so bad, was it?
是的
No.
考虑到你是个好女孩
And now because you've been such a good girl,
我想我该给你个惊喜
I think it's time for a surprise.
Claire  这边  我们走这边
Claire, this way. Here we go.
在这儿
Over here.
这是哪儿?
What is this place?
-这是给你的孩子的  Claire   -噢  太不可思议了
-It's for your baby, Claire.  -Oh, it's amazing.
Charlie怎么样了?
What...what happened to Charlie?
Charlie?  噢  他很好
Charlie? Oh, he's fine.
当我们离营地够远时  我让他回去
When we got far enough from camp, I let him go back.
那么这些都是从哪儿来的?
So where did it all come from?
我很乐意解释给你听  Claire
Well, I'd love to explain everything to you, Claire,
但是我想现在对你来说还太难以接受了
but I'm afraid it would be a little overwhelming right now.
来吧  打开它
Go ahead, turn it on.
等我一下  我马上回来
Wait here. I'll be right back.
到底发生了什么?
What the hell happened?
你应该列出一个名单  然后把她算上 是我没说清楚么?
You were supposed to make the list and then bring her in. Was I unclear?
这不是我的错
It's not my fault.
他们知道我不是飞机上的 他们有旅客名单
They knew I wasn't on the plane. They had a manifest.
那么我该怎么和他说?
Well, what am I supposed to tell him?
你知道他了解后会怎么做? 该死的  Ethan
You know what he's gonna do when he finds out? Damn it, Ethan.
出去
Get out.
快离开这儿
Get out of here.
Claire?
Claire  你还好吧?
Claire, are you all right?
我  呃...
I, um...
可以走了么?
Ready to go?
亲爱的 嘘 妈妈要走了 亲爱的 好吗
Hey, sweetheart, shh, mommy's gotta go now, sweetheart, okay?
别哭了  别哭了  没事的
Shh, don't cry. Don't cry. It's okay.
我马上就回来  我会让你变好的 好么?
I'll be back really soon. And I'll make you feel all better, okay?
我保证
I promise.
谢谢
Thanks.
好的
Okay.
-你还好吧?  -是的
-You okay?  -Yeah.
你肯定她是往这儿走的么?
Are you sure this is her trail?
我们是从把她赶走的地方开始找的
We started at the exact spot where we chased her off the beach.
那么你对Rousseau了解多少?
So what do you know about Rousseau?
不多
Not much.
你去"黑岩石"那儿时  你们一直呆在一起
You spent all that time with her when you went out to "the Black Rock."
你们肯定说了什么
You must have talked about something.
她的船在这儿撞毁了...
Just  about her ship crashing here...
她和她的研究队束手无策
her and her research team getting stranded.
他们怎么了?
What happened to them?
他们死了
They died.
怎么死的?
How?
我们跟丢了
Tracks are gone. Trail ends here.
Kate  他们是怎么死的?
Kate, how did they die?
她杀了他们
She killed them.
什么?
What?
-为什么...为什么她...  -因为他们被感染了
-Why...why would she...  -Because they were infected.
你现在相信我了  是么?
You believe me now, don't you?
我要你带我回那儿去
I want you to take me back there.
回去?
Back?
-去我抓伤你的地方   -Claire...
-To where I scratched you.   -Claire...
不  好了  我记起来了  她知道的
No, okay, she knows I remember.
我现在记起很多事了
I remember a lot of it now.
我记得一个房间  药物  一个年轻女孩
I remember the room, the medicine, a teenage girl.
好了  所以别骗我
Okay, so don't lie to me
别假装你听不懂我说什么
and make out you don't know what I'm talking about.
我孩子病了   你现在马上带我去那儿拿我要的药物
My baby is sick, and you're gonna take me back there to get what he needs right now.
那地方离这儿不远
It's not far from here.
能和你谈一下么?
may I have a word with you?
当然
Sure.
他是谁?
Who is he?
什么?
What?
你藏在舱子里的那个人
The man that you are keeping in the hatch.
Locke和你说...
Did Locke tell you...
Locke没和我说任何事  他是谁?
Locke did not tell me anything. Who is he?
我们不知道
We don't know.
我想和他说话
I wish to speak to him.
和他说什么?
Speak to him about what?
我想单独和他说
I wish to speak to him alone.
你能安排么?
Can you arrange this?
我为什么要安排?
Why should I do that?
因为你想让这件事保密
Because you wish to keep this a secret.
我们为什么停在这儿?
Why are we stopping here?
这就是你抓伤我的地方
This  is where you scratched me.
但是这儿什么都没有
But there's nothing here.
我们下面去哪儿?
Where do we go next?
你为什么问我?
Why are you asking me that?
你得告诉我去哪儿
You need to tell me where to go!
房间在哪儿?
Where is this room?!
你怎么能那么说?
Look, how can you be saying that?
好了  你抱着我  所以我抓了你...
Okay, you grabbed me. That's why I scratched you...
因为你要把我带回他们那里去
because you were taking me back to them!
这是你认为的么?
Is that what you think?
你说你记起来了
You said you remembered.
所以我带你来这里
That's why I brought you here.
你骗了我
You lied!
把你的手拿开
Get your hands off of her.
开枪吧
Go ahead.
求你了
Please.
Claire
醒醒
Wake up.
怎么样了?
How's it coming?
一个做好了  还剩一个
One down. One to go.
现在我们就缺一只小脚把它穿上了 不是么?
Now all's we need is a little foot to put it on, huh?
我跟你说...
Tell you what...
我们偷偷出去散散步  你说好么?
what do you say we sneak out of here and take a walk?
好的
Okay.
我很抱歉现在才安排你出来
I'm sorry this is the first time I've managed to get you out.
我的朋友怕你会逃跑
My friends are afraid you'll run away.
-别出卖我  好么?    -好的
-Don't tell on me, okay?    -Oh, okay.
休息一下
Whoa. Easy now.
慢点  慢点
Easy. Easy! Whoa.
好了
Okay.
好了  给你  你需要的
Okay, here. This'll help.
谢谢
Thanks.
怎么了?
What?
-太酸了  -是么?
-That is really sour.  -Is it?
我没注意到
I hadn't noticed.
好无聊
Blah.
嘿...他在踢我
Hey...he's kicking.
-可以么?    -恩...
-May I?    -Yeah...
Claire  可以告诉你个秘密么?
Claire, can I tell you a secret?
好的
Yes.
我会想念你的  我...
I'm gonna miss you. I wi...
你希望你可以不要走
I wish you didn't have to go.
也许我不需要走
Maybe I don't have to go.
我们一起经历了这些  Claire
We've been through this, Claire.
给你和你孩子的疫苗不够用了
There's not enough vaccine for you and the baby.
但是我...我没病啊
But I'm not...I'm not sick.
谢天谢地
Thank god.
一旦你孩子生下来之后 你就可以回你朋友那儿了
And once you've delivered, you can go back to your friends,
希望你会没事
and hopefully you'll stay that way.
如果我要看孩子呢?
What...what if I want to see the baby?
除非你愿意  没人可以把他带走
Hey, nobody's going to take him from you unless that's what you want.
你有你的选择
You have a choice.
我们是好人  Claire
We're good people, Claire.
我们是一个好家庭
We're a good family.
如果你信任我们  就可以把孩子留下
But if you're gonna trust us with your child,
我要你肯定
I want you to be sure.
好么?
Okay?
我肯定
Sure.
你在这儿啊
There you are.
你去哪儿?
Where are you going?
我知道在哪儿  在这儿
I know this is it. It's here.
Claire
Claire!
让她去
Leave her alone.
-什么?    -让她去找
-Excuse me?    -Let her look.
找什么?
Look for what?
Claire
手电筒
Flashlights.
有灯  我看看能不能打开电源
There are lights. I'm gonna see if I can turn the power on.
你还好吧?
Are you okay?
这边
This way.
这是哪儿?
What is this place?
这是他们为我孩子准备的
It's where they were gonna keep him.
醒醒
Wake up.
-你是谁?  -嘘  他们会听见的
-Who are you?  -Shh! They'll hear you.
听着  你得离开这儿
Look, you have to get out of here.
你现在得马上离开这儿
You have to get out of here now!
-什...不不不  我不能走  -你可以的  快点
-What...no, no, no. I can't leave.  -Yes, you can. Come on.
我不能走  不  停下  你在干什么
I can't leave. No! Stop. What are you doing?
别叫
Don't scream.
他们今晚就要做了
They're gonna do it tonight.
什么?  做什么?
What? Do what?
你在说什么?
What are you talking about? Ow!
你会死的  他们要把你孩子弄出来
You're going to die. They're gonna cut him out of you.
我可以带你回你营地  但是我们得马上走
I can get you back to your camp, but we have to leave now.
不不不  你骗人 你骗人 我相信他们
No, no, no! Hey, you're lying. You're lying, okay? I'm sure about this.
Ethan在哪儿?  我想和Ethan谈谈 Ethan不会伤害我的
Where's Ethan? I want to talk to Ethan. Ethan wouldn't hurt me.
有一天你会感谢我的
You'll thank me for this one day.
这是疫苗  我们得防止他生病
It's a vaccine. We don't want him to get sick.
在这儿了
It's here.
药在这儿了
The medicine's here.
帮帮我
Help me.
Help!
Kate  来这儿  帮帮我
Kate! Come here! I need some help!
帮我搬起来
Help me up with this.
这是什么?
What is it?
在这儿  疫苗在这里面
It's in here. The vaccine's in here.
-好了  来吧  -好的
-Okay. Come on.  -Okay.
1  2  3
One, two, three!
好了
Okay.
是在这的  疫苗应该在这里的
It was in here. The vaccine was in here!
它在...在哪儿  在哪儿  在哪儿?
It was in...where is it, where is it, where is it?
疫苗在这里面  它去哪儿了?
The vaccine was in here! Where is it?!
你带我回这儿来的  它在哪儿?
You were bringing me back here. Where is it?!
你知道的  是么?
You know where it is, don't you?
告诉我  告诉我它在哪儿  告诉我
Tell me! Tell me where it is! Tell me!
Ethan?
Ethan
Ethan  我肯定
Ethan, I'm sure.
Ethan
嘿  嘿  Ethan
Hey! Hey, Ethan!
我...我肯定我要...我要你把孩子带走
I'm...I'm sure I want...I want you to take the baby.
Ethan
你...你是谁?
Who are...who are you?
-Claire    -我在这儿
-Claire!    -Yeah! I'm here!
我听到你了  你在哪儿?
I can hear you! Where are you?
安静点
Be quiet.
-我在这儿  Ethan    -安静点
-I'm here, Ethan!   -Be quiet.
不 不  没事的  我要把孩子给他们
No, no. It's okay. I have to give him to them.
我要把孩子给他们  这样他就安全了
I have to give him to them so he'll be safe, okay?
救命  我在这儿  Ethan
Help! I'm here! Ethan!
-住手  -不
-Stop!  -No!
你不是...想把我带回去  是么?
You weren't...trying to take me back, were you?
你想救我
You were trying to save me.
我背着你回你们营地
I carried you on my back to your camp.
在他们可以找到你的地方放下你
I left youwhere they would find you.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
你去哪儿?
Where are you going?
你不是唯一一个没有找到要找的东西的人
You're not the only one who didn't find what they were looking for.
我只能走到这儿了
This is as far as I go.
你的孩子...
Your baby...
是个女孩么?
was it a girl?
是的
Yes.
她叫什么?
What was her name?
Alex...
Alexandra
我记得一个女孩...一个蓝眼睛的女孩
I remember a girl...a girl with blue eyes?
她  她救了我  她救了我...就像你做的
She, uh, she helped me. She saved me... just like you did.
她不像那些其他人  她是好人
She wasn't like the others. She was good.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry
你没有找到你想找的
that you didn't find what you were looking for.
我希望你的孩子没有被感染
And I hope your baby's not infected.
但是如果真的被感染了...
But if it is...
我希望你知道该怎么做
I hope you know what must be done.
还要工具?
Back for more tools?
他知道了  John
He knows, John.
恩  进去吧
Well, there you go.
小心点和他说
Be careful what you say to him.
他又聪明又好奇
He's smart and curious.
你好了就叫我们
Just give us a shout when you're done.
并且警报响起的时候
And if the alarm goes off,
别告诉他是怎么回事
don't tell him what it's for.
警报是怎么回事?
What is it for?
你好
Hello.
我是Eko先生
I am Mr.Eko.
Henry Gale
不介意我坐下吧  Henry?
Do you mind if I sit, Henry?
你在这里面多久了?
How long have you been in here?
2天
Two days.
他们对你好么?
Are they treating you well?
对我好么?
Treating me well?
我是...是个囚犯
I'm a...a prisoner.
并且我不知道为什么...
And I don't know why or for what...
你成了囚犯是因为他们很小心
You are a prisoner because they are being careful.
他们很小心是因为他们认为你在说谎
They are being careful because they believe you are lying.
我为什么说谎?
Why would I lie?
他们认为我是..."其他人"中的一个? 其他什么人?
They think I'm one of these..."others"? Other what?
别讲了  Henry
Please stop talking, Henry.
我在这个岛上的第一天
The first night I spent on this island,
我被两个人带到了丛林里
I was dragged into the jungle by two men.
他们一个字都没和我说  我也没和他们说话
They never spoke a word to me, nor I to them.
我杀了他们...
I killed these men...
用石头砸他们的头
smashed in their head with a stone,
手上沾满了他们的血
felt their blood on my arms.
我要你知道
I need you to know
事后我是多么的内疚
how sorry I am for this.
我要你知道我现在已经重新做人了
I need you to know that I am back on a righteous path now
并且我为以前的作为感到后悔
and that I regret my actions.
我希望得到你的宽恕
I ask you for your forgiveness.
你为什么和我说这些?
Why are you telling me this?
因为我需要和某个人说
Because I needed to tell someone.
他看起来很好  热度降下来了
He looks good. Fever's broken.
皮疹也消退了
The rash has even started to fade.
非常谢谢你
Thank you so much.
我什么也没做
I didn't do anything.
我过几个小时再来  好么?
I'll, uh, check back in a couple of hours, okay?
看看
Look.
你还在我肚子里时  妈妈帮你做的
Mommy made this for you when you were still inside her tummy. Yeah.
你知道么?  我想让他们带走你
You know what? I wanted them to take you.
但现在我知道了...
But now I know...
现在我知道我们应该在一起
now I know that we're supposed to be together,
你和我
you and me.
我们应该互相照顾  好么?
We're supposed to take care of each other, okay?
你是我的  我爱你  我非常爱你
You're mine, and I love you. I love you so much.
-没有三明治?   -没有
-No cheeseburgers, huh?   -No cheeseburgers.
还不错
Bon appit.
你说Hemingway的事是真的么?
Is that true what you said about Hemingway?
-你听力不错  -是门太薄了
-You have good ears.  -You have thin doors.
-你看过Hemingway的书?  -当然
-You read Hemingway?  -Sure.
跟着公牛后面跑的人们   在西班牙内战时奋勇拼搏...
Guy ran with the bulls, fought in the spanish civil war...
那些我可以全身心投入 这些我却看不到5页
stuff I can wrap my brain around. This I can't get through five pages of.
Dostoevsky也有他的优点
Hmm. Dostoevsky had his virtues, too.
他也是个天才
He was a genius, for one.
斗牛不是全部
Bullfighting isn't everything.
那么你是哪一个?
So which one are you?
什么?
I'm sorry?
你是个天才么?
Are you the genius?
或者说你是一个 感到生活在天才阴影下的人?
Or are you the guy who always feels like he's living in the shadow of the genius?
我是...
I was...
我不太擅长做大量的文字分析
I was never very muchinto literary analysis.
我只是不知道为什么你受那个医生的指使
I just don't understand why you let the doctor call the shots.
没人在指使谁
No one calls the shots.
Jack是和我一起做抉择的
Jack and imake decisions together.
好的
Right. Okay.
是我弄错了
My mistake.
==============|  YYeTs字幕组招募启示  |==============
英文字幕录制(居住在加拿大和美国)  双语字幕校正   时间轴调整
英语翻译   欧美影视新闻翻译  影视评论  论坛版主  美工人员
服务器提供者  发布宣传  联系地址：www.YYeTs.com
==== YYeTs属于网络爱好者组织 加入者仅凭个人兴趣爱好 无报酬 ====